https://www.cabinet.com/terms-of-service/

Our Commitment
Cabinet.com, and related sites including Get Classifieds!, recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about you, our customers and prospects. This customer privacy policy is intended to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information against our users? reasonable expectations of privacy.
General User Information
In general, we gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas users visit most often and what services users access the most. We only use such data in the aggregate. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for our users. We may share this information with our advertisers and collaborators, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may understand how Cabinet.com users, collectively, use our site and our services.
Personal Information
While visiting any of the Cabinet.com Web sites (collectively, the “site”), we may ask you to register and/or provide information that personally identifies you (“personal information”) for purposes of interacting with the site. Such personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, street address, and e-mail address. On any page that collects personal information, we will specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service, enter you in the promotion you have requested, or respond to your inquiry or comment.
What are Cookies?
A cookie is a small data text file that a Web site sends to your browser, which is stored on your system. The site can only access the information from a cookie sent by the site. We cannot access cookies sent by other Web sites or the information contained therein. Additionally, we cannot learn your e-mail address or any other information about you through the use of a cookie. The only way we would learn such information is if you specifically and voluntarily submit that information to us, for example, through a registration system, or by entering a sweepstakes or promotion.
We use an advertising server developed by a third party to display ads on the site. Some of these ads may contain cookies that are sent by third parties (e.g. advertising agencies or advertising clients). We do not have access to these cookies or any information that they contain. We encourage you to contact the advertiser or its privacy policy for more information on these cookies. Links from other Web sites that appear on the site may also send cookies; but we do not control such activities.
Why does the site use cookies? Cabinet.com uses cookies to track usage of the site and further personalize your experience when you are visiting the site. By tracking usage, we can best determine what features of the site best serve the users.
What benefits do I receive from cookies? Overall, the use of cookies helps to give you a more personalized experience at the site. The information is used to keep our site fresh and relevant to you the user. Cookies also identify you to our server, allowing you to avoid retyping your e-mail address and password each time you access the site.
May I decline to accept a cookie? You may decline to accept cookies sent by the site by selecting an option on your browser to reject cookies. However, portions of the site which require registration will not be accessible to you. In such cases, we ask that you register and provide us with basic information on our registration page, or sign in if previously registered. Cookies enable our server to know that you are a registered user, and will eliminate the need for you to log in each time you access our site.
IP Addresses: The Telegraph Online logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes and to determine site usage. Your IP address does not contain personal information about you.
Use of Personal Information
We believe in protecting your privacy, and will not share personal information with third parties outside of Cabinet.com except as described in this Privacy Policy. We believe we can enhance your experience on our site with the information you share with us. We use personal information about you to improve our advertising and marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to personalize the site’s content, layout, and services. We may also use your personal information, such as your e-mail address or mailing address, to contact you regarding products and/or services that may be of interest to you, to respond to an inquiry from you regarding the information that we have collected, or respond to your comments and suggestions.
Cabinet.com may match specific and/or aggregated personal information with third party data to provide you with product and content offerings that interest you and improve our advertising and marketing efforts. Cabinet.com also may disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to potential advertisers, partners, other third parties, our affiliate companies, and for other lawful purposes.
As part of your experience on our site, you may receive communications from us related to products and services that might interest you. While we believe these services will enhance your experience at our site, you will at all times be able to opt out from receiving these communications, either by specifically opting out of these services or by deleting your profile from our database. Please refer to “opting-out” for further reference.
We have today, and will in the future have, arrangements with third party service providers, such as credit card processors, shipping companies and fulfillment services. When you sign up for a service we offer on the site, we may be required to share personal information with that service provider in order to provide the service. These third party providers are required to comply with this policy and protect your information in the same way we do. They are not permitted to retain or use personal information for any purpose unrelated to providing the service.
Cabinet.com may also offer other services as a part of our site (e.g., job finder service, personalized finance and weather information alerts, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions with unaffiliated third parties). If you choose to use these optional services or opportunities, we may provide some of your personal information to these parties. We will not do so without telling you in advance, and you can avoid having us make such disclosures by choosing not to use these services or features of the site. Some of these third parties may also collect their own personal information in connection with providing the service. We encourage you to check the applicable privacy policy for that portion of the site prior to disclosing personal information. Please refer to “Party Collecting the Information” for further reference.
We may provide personal information to our affiliated companies in order to improve our marketing and advertising efforts and your experience with our site. Although this privacy policy generally applies only to Cabinet.com and its related sites, and not to activities or information collected by our offline partners, in the event we share personal information you provide us on the site, we will require that our affiliated companies comply with this policy with respect to that information and protect your information in the same way we do.
We reserve the right to disclose personal information when needed to comply with the law or a legal process, cooperate with investigations of purported unlawful activities, to identify persons violating the law, or in connection with the sale of part or all of Cabinet.com or its affiliate’s stock or assets.
Party Collecting the Information
This privacy policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose any information to other parties, whether through, for example, online auctions, chat rooms, personal ads, or the like, through third party services or promotions offered on or through the site or through other Web sites throughout the Internet, different policies may apply and Cabinet.com shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of such information.
The site may offer forums, message boards, or chat rooms as one of the services on the site. If you disclose personal information in one of these forums, this information can be viewed, collected, and used by others. Cabinet.com is not responsible for the use of information you disclose in these forums. We encourage you to consult the forum rules regarding the policies and procedures that apply to that portion of the site.
Our sites may operate as part of a larger group of sites, and may carry co-branded pages. In addition, other sites may use the site’s or The Cabinet’s name. Since Cabinet.com does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies, if any, of such third parties, and Cabinet.com shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of your private information by such parties. Therefore, we encourage you to ask questions and review those parties’ privacy policies before you disclose your personal information to others.
Links to Other Materials
Third party sites linked to and from the site are not necessarily under the control of the Cabinet.com. Therefore, Cabinet.com shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. Cabinet.com does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the site, you do so entirely at your own risk.
Children’s Privacy
We do not specifically collect information about children under 13 in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. We believe that children should get their parents? consent before giving out personal information. We further believe that parents should participate, and guide their children?s experience on Cabinet.com. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practicable.
Opting-Out
We respect your privacy and ability to choose whether to share information with us and any third party. You may choose to “opt-out” of sharing personal information in several ways. When choosing to use certain features or services on the site, you can choose whether to share optional personal information in connection with the feature or service. If you receive communications from us that you prefer not to receive, you may opt out from receiving these communications, by modifying the contact options in your registration profile.
You may “opt-out” altogether from providing personal information to us by not registering on the site and thereby not providing personal information. You may also choose at a later date to have your name removed from our database by deleting your registration profile. To do so, please follow the process described in “Edit Member Profile.”
Certain portions of the site and certain services provided on the site, however, do require registration in order to access or use these areas and services. If you choose not to register or provide certain information, these areas will not be accessible to you.
Security
Cabinet.com maintains industry standard safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the personal information that you provide to us.
Feedback
We have several feedback forms on the Cabinet.com. Any feedback that is submitted through these forms or through email is the property of Cabinet.com. We may use this feedback for marketing purposes, or to contact you for additional feedback.
Privacy Policy Changes and Contact
Changes to this privacy policy will be posted here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about the Cabinet.com’s privacy policy, please feel free to email us at privacy@nh.com or call (603) 594-6458 and speak to our new media manager.
MOST READ
Memo Foundation skate bowl breaks ground at Keyes
Scouting for Food
Bakery challenging mask mandate fine
Elections were fair and free
D-H launches mask campaign
Sununu disappoints on COVID
News
Copyright © The Cabinet Press | https://www.cabinet.com | 167 Elm Street, Milford, NH 03055 | 603-673-3100 | Ogden Newspapers | The Nutting Company
